<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>Happy Apps</title>
    <description>Designing products and teams, the human centric way</description>
    <link>https://jsooriah.github.io/happyapps</link>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:44:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <ttl>250</ttl>
    <atom:link href="https://jsooriah.github.io/happyappsrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

<item>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jsooriah.github.io/happyapps/blog/posts/dont-go-chasing-waterfalls-and-turn-the-ship-around/</guid>
    <title><![CDATA[ Don&#39;t go chasing waterfalls and turn the ship around ]]></title>
    <description><![CDATA[ Historically, many organisations operated with a waterfall-like model where product managers or business analysts would create detailed specifications that engineers would implement. Engineering teams would receive “clearer guidance upfront” with regular check-ins to ensure alignment. This approach treats engineers primarily as implementers who translate requirements into code. ]]></description>
    <link>https://jsooriah.github.io/happyapps/blog/posts/dont-go-chasing-waterfalls-and-turn-the-ship-around/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jsooriah.github.io/happyapps/blog/posts/root-cause-analysis-in-product-management-learning-the-hard-way/</guid>
    <title><![CDATA[ Root Cause Analysis In Product Management Learning The Hard Way ]]></title>
    <description><![CDATA[ As tech people, we’re often eager to build. The excitement of creating something new, something that showcases our technical capabilities and vision, can be intoxicating. But sometimes, our rush to solution-building can blind us to the fundamental question that should drive every product decision:What problem are we really solving? ]]></description>
    <link>https://jsooriah.github.io/happyapps/blog/posts/root-cause-analysis-in-product-management-learning-the-hard-way/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jsooriah.github.io/happyapps/blog/posts/the-evolution-of-ux-in-the-age-of-ai-from-interfaces-to-intelligence/</guid>
    <title><![CDATA[ The Evolution of UX in the Age of AI - From Interfaces to Intelligence ]]></title>
    <description><![CDATA[ Users don’t fundamentally care about your interface — they care about what it helps them accomplish. Nobody opens Photoshop because they love its toolbar; they open it because they need to edit an image. The interface is just the mediator between intention and result. This realization brings us to a critical inflection point - What if our obsession with UI elements has been missing the bigger picture of UX — the holistic user experience? What if AI could help us transcend the limitations of traditional interfaces to focus directly on user outcomes? ]]></description>
    <link>https://jsooriah.github.io/happyapps/blog/posts/the-evolution-of-ux-in-the-age-of-ai-from-interfaces-to-intelligence/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
